{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5209","name":"El Club","address":"4114 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209","owner":"EFG Group","licenseNumber":"203410","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":null,"establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.09363,42.32139","geojson":{"id":"5209","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.093627777,42.321392594]},"properties":{"name":"El Club","owner":"EFG Group","address":"4114 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"203410","establishmentid":"5209","establishment_type":null,"establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"5/12/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"794","name":"Armando's Mexican Restaurant","address":"4242 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5308","name":"Mangonadas Del Barrio #1, LLC","address":"4029 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"470","name":"Neveria La Michoacana","address":"4336 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5409","name":"PizzaPlex","address":"4454 W Vernor","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"5387","name":"Flowers of Vietnam","address":"4430 W Vernor","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"822","name":"Western Senior High School","address":"1500 Scotten Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1307","name":"Amicci's Pizza","address":"3849 W Vernor","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"979","name":"Clippert Academy","address":"1981 McKinstry St","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5402","name":"Antojitos Los Tres Hermanos","address":"4627 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3711","name":"Little Caesar's #166","address":"4635 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50162","inspectionDate":"2019-12-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Screening that is sixteen mesh to the inch or greater","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"SCREEN DOOR","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"47889","inspectionDate":"2019-05-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Air/water thermometer(s)","subItem":"cooler reach in","problemDescription":"Not accurate","subProblem":"To plus or minus 2 degrees f","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Calibrate to requirement above."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"holes or gaps along floors","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"44143","inspectionDate":"2018-11-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-11-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"holes or gaps along floors","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ice machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-11-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."}]},{"inspectionid":"42092","inspectionDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-303.11","violationDescription":"After use as a medium for cooling the exterior surfaces of FOOD, or cooling coils and tubes of EQUIPMENT, ice may not be used as FOOD. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ice","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used as a cooling medium","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cannot be used for food"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"}]},{"inspectionid":"39308","inspectionDate":"2017-07-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5209"}}